Guide to the New Dramatists Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, 1949-1996; Series II; 114.58; (100 boxes) + 12 broadside folders
  - Financial Records
    - Recommendations, 1986-1989 (Box 91)
    - Internships
      - Intern miscellaneous, undated (Box 91)
      - Critique file, undated (Box 91)
      - Intern welcome letters, undated (Box 91)
      - Intern applicants, 1987-1988 (Box 91)
      - Blank intern applications, undated (Box 91)
      - General intern information, undated (Box 91)
      - Blank letters of agreement, undated; 2 (Box 91)
      - Intern flyer: original, 1987 (Box 91)
      - Intern play evaluations, undated (Box 91)
      - Internship information, 1985-1986; 3 (Box 91)
      - Interns to be contacted, 1988-1989 (Box 91)
      - Intern information and applications, undated (Box 91)
      - Intern letter of agreement, undated (Box 91)
      - Fall interns, 1988 (Box 91)
      - Intern time sheets, undated (Box 92)
      - Glasfeld, Andrew, 1989 (Box 92)
      - Work Experience Program/ Ferrara, Jean, 1988-1989 (Box 92)
      - Maldonado, Audrey, undated (Box 92)
      - Beldner, Jeffrey Mark, undated (Box 92)
      - Resumes (Box 92)
    - Cash receipts, undated (Box 92)
    - Check stubs, undated (Box 92)
    - Hoffman Travel Services, Inc., 1987 (Box 92)
    - Promo 87, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Office supplies miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 92)
    - New York Telephone bills, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Leslie Supply Company, Inc., 1986 (Box 92)
    - Printing, duplications, and framing, undated (Box 92)
    - DeWitt Stern, Gutmann & Company, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Xerox, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Audit, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Postage, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Travel, 1987 (Box 92)
    - HYH Contracting, Inc., 1987 (Box 92)
    - Montgomery Ward, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous taxes paid, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Miscellaneous bills, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Vendor billing correspondence, 1987 February (Box 92)
    - Luncheon, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Village Voice/ Times, 1987 (Box 92)
    - F. Weidner & Sons, 1987 (Box 92)
    - S. Wolf's Sons, 1987 (Box 92)
    - La Charade, undated (Box 92)
    - Loan Agreements- not paid (Box 92)
    - Stanley Young Loan Fund, 1983-1986 (Box 92)
    - Contemporary Office & Business Machine Co., 1987 (Box 92)
    - Dana Commercial Credit (Canon copy machine), 1987 (Box 92)
    - Digital Equipment, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Discount Messenger Service., 1987 (Box 92)
    - Delson Business Systems Inc., 1987 (Box 92)
    - Drama Books, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Dyke's Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Fees, permits, and insurance, 1986 (Box 92)
    - New York Telephone 974-9874, 1985-1987 (Box 92)
    - New York Telephone 664-9415, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - IND expenses, 1987 (Box 92)
    - IBM, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Imprint Copy Corp., 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Isotec, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Janovic Plaza, 1987 (Box 92)
    - J.B. Contracting Co., 1986 (Box 92)
    - Kingsmill Paper Corp., 1986 (Box 92)
    - Doodles expenses, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Chowder Party, 1989 (Box 92)
    - The Christina Crawford Foundation, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Capital improvement, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Wayne M. Cribb, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Room/space rentals, 1985 (Box 92)
    - Rental reports, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Con Edison, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Cory Coffee, 1986-1987 (Box 92)
    - Seventh Heaven Inc., 1987 (Box 92)
    - Allnet, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Bank Statement Fund, 1986 (Box 92)
    - B&S Office Supply Inc., 1986 (Box 92)
    - J.J. Bender Associates (Box 92)
    - Books and periodicals purchased, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Ogilvy and Mather, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Delinquency notice from the city collections office, 1986 (Box 92)
    - Class information, 1987 (Box 92)
    - Check copies, 1984; 2 (Box 92)
    - Final report of cost per playwright, 1985-1986 (Box 92)
    - Industry drive, 1985-1986 (Box 92)
    - Xerox bill, 1985 (Box 92)
    - Critics list, 1980 (Box 92)
    - Financial updates, 1982 (Box 92)
    - Fund raising expenses, 1983-1984; 2 (Box 93)
    - Real estate taxes, 1984; 2 (Box 93)
    - Phone service information, 1982-1988 (Box 93)
    - Journal advertising insertion order, 1984 April 13 (Box 93)
    - Balance sheets, 1984-1985 (Box 93)
    - General ledgers, 1982 (Box 93)
    - Final report, 1985-1986 (Box 93)
    - Fund and financial monthly reports, 1988 (Box 93)
    - Composer- librettist, 1985 (Box 93)
    - Exchanges, 1986 (Box 93)
    - ADP, undated (Box 93)
    - Court transcript, 1989 (Box 93)
    - Allnet, 1986-1987 (Box 93)
    - Loans to playwrights and information, 1982-1986 (Box 93)
    - Doodles auction, undated (Box 93)
    - Luncheon, 1986 (Box 93)
    - Insurance, 1987 (Box 93)
    - Various single purchases, 1986 (Box 93)
    - Theatre Communications Group Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 93)
    - New York Telephone bill, undated (Box 93)
    - Mileage reimbursement sheets, 1987 (Box 93)
    - ScriptShare, 1986-1987 (Box 93)
    - Check requests, 1987 (Box 93)
    - Service Agreement with Delson Business Systems Inc., 1987 (Box 93)
    - Check copies, 1986 August (Box 93)
    - Writers' retreat, 1989 (Box 93)
    - Audit/liability information, 1986-1988 (Box 93)
    - Budget, 1987 (Box 93)
    - Opera workshop, 1987 (Box 93)
    - Bills, 1982-1984 (Box 93)
    - Forms, 1985 (Box 93)
    - Memos, 1985 (Box 93)
    - Schiff, Harold, undated (Box 93)
    - Cash receipts, 1982 (Box 93)
    - Check file, 1987-1988 (Box 93)
    - Labels for over $250 contributions, undated (Box 93)
    - C/R Journal, 1981 (Box 93)
    - Monthly reports, 1982 (Box 93)
    - Cash disbursements, 1982 (Box 93)
    - Cash disbursements (Box 94)
    - New York Telephone 757-6960, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - SVG Computer Supplies Ltd., 1985 (Box 94)
    - Traden Stationers, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Theatre Communications Group Inc., 1986 (Box 94)
    - Thico, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Readings/programs and cast biographies, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Triton, 1986 (Box 94)
    - UPS, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Village Voice, 1986 (Box 94)
    - F. Weidwer & Sons, 1986 (Box 94)
    - S. Wolf's Sons, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Xerox (typewriter supplies), 1987 (Box 94)
    - In-kind donations, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Staff meeting agenda, 1986 (Box 94)
    - New York Telephone 664-9415, undated (Box 94)
    - Nu-Way Copy Center, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Office supplies miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Pitney Bowes, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Postage receipts, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Quad center, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Quick Quality Copies, 1986 (Box 94)
    - R&M miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 94)
    - The Players Club, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Retax, 1986-1987 (Box 94)
    - Safeguard, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - Fred M. Schildwachter & Sons, Inc., 1985 (Box 94)
    - Richard J. Sica, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Silver & Sons, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Star-Litho, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Straight Hardware, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Isotec, undated (Box 94)
    - Joint purchasing updates, 1986 (Box 94)
    - H. Jonas, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Kingsmill Paper, 1986 (Box 94)
    - R. Kopitchinski, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Leslie Supply, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - Menash, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Miscellaneous bills, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Christie Mullen, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - National Information Data Center, undated (Box 94)
    - The Drama Book Shop, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - Dyke's Lumber Company, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Federal Express, undated (Box 94)
    - Herb Field Studio, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Fire extinguisher service, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Gestetner, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - Hardware invoices, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - HYH Contracting, 1984-1986 (Box 94)
    - J.J. Bender Associates, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - B.I.G. Office Supplies, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield, 1985-1986; 2 (Box 94)
    - Cam Computer Supplies, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Con Edison, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Cory Coffee, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Digital Equipment, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - Messenger and postage bills, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Do Best Printing Corporation, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Schedules, 1985 (Box 94)
    - Check requests, undated (Box 94)
    - Art Flag Company, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Bank statements, 1987 (Box 94)
    - Publication requests, undated (Box 94)
    - AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - Unsorted mail, undated (Box 94)
    - B&S Office Supply, 1986 (Box 94)
    - Allnet, 1985-1986 (Box 94)
    - IBM, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Imprint Copy Corp., 1986 (Box 95)
    - Isotec, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Script readings, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Luncheon expenses, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Program expenses, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Playwright travel, 1986 (Box 95)
    - American Arts Alliance dues, 1985 (Box 95)
    - In-house calendars, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Billy Rose expenses, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Doodle expenses, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Accounts payable, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Petty cash receipts, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Playwrights' press, 1988-1989 (Box 95)
    - Script reading, 1986-1987 (Box 95)
    - Rental income, 1987 (Box 95)
    - Fund-raising receipts, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Fund-raising expenses general, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Thank-you letters for contributions, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Industry drive, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Literary expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Executive director reimbursement requests, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Typewriter inventory, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Chair inventory, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Teachers and expenses, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Seventh heaven inventory, undated (Box 95)
    - 1099 file, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Board of directors, 1977-1985 (Box 95)
    - Classes, 1986 spring (Box 95)
    - Seventh heaven receipts, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Class receipts, 1985 fall (Box 95)
    - Alumni, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Nancy audit letters, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Phone and copier bills, 1986 (Box 95)
    - ScriptShare, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Luncheon journal advertisers to be billed, undated (Box 95)
    - Annual spring luncheon, undated (Box 95)
    - Luncheon report, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Bequests, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Classes, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Spring students, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Luncheon committee, 1988 (Box 95)
    - Luncheon thank-you letters to be done, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Invitation information, 1986 (Box 95)
    - National Benefit Life Insurance Company, 1986 (Box 95)
    - Monologue book agreements, 1987 (Box 95)
    - Balance sheets, 1987-1988 (Box 95)
    - General ledger, 1987 (Box 95)
    - Check requests, 1986-1987 (Box 95)
    - Insurance, 1987 (Box 95)
    - Literary services monthly expense reports, 1985-1986 (Box 95)
    - Financial statements, 1985-1984 (Box 95)
    - General fund balance sheets, 1984-1985 (Box 95)
    - Artist reimbursement, 1987 (Box 95)
    - Taxes, 1988-1989 (Box 95)
    - Bank record, 1988 (Box 95)
    - Miscellaneous expenses, 1989 (Box 95)
    - Petty cash, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Receivables, 1988 (Box 95)
    - Thomas Dunn expenses, 1985 (Box 95)
    - Matching gifts, 1988 (Box 95)
    - Financial information, 1985-1986 (Box 96)
    - 1099, 1985 (Box 96)
    - Financial and bank records, 1986 (Box 96)
    - Checks received, 1986; 2 folders (Box 96)
    - Financial correspondence, 1986 (Box 96)
    - Taxes, unemployment, etc., 1985 (Box 96)
    - Tax records, 1985-1986 (Box 96)
    - Check request forms, 1985 (Box 96)
    - Receipts and records of scripts read, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
    - Financial notes, undated (Box 96)
    - Financial balance sheets, 1985 (Box 96)
    - Cash disbursement journals, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
    - Check requests, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Cast contact sheets, 1983 (Box 96)
    - Checks paid, 1983 (Box 96)
    - Quarterly expense reports, 1982 (Box 96)
    - Artist reimbursement, 1982 (Box 96)
    - Literary services monthly expenses, 1983-1984 (Box 96)
    - Earned income and contributions, 1983-1984 (Box 96)
    - Literary panelists fees, 1984 (Box 96)
    - Woodruff, Robert, 1984-1985 (Box 96)
    - Literary reimbursement, 1982 (Box 96)
    - Earned income and cash contributions, 1982-1983 (Box 96)
    - Artists fees, 1982 (Box 96)
    - Travel expenses, 1983-1984 (Box 96)
    - Unemployment files, 1982-1984 (Box 96)
    - Abbott, George, 1986 (Box 96)
    - Board meetings, 1987 (Box 96)
    - Industry fund drive, 1980 (Box 96)
    - "Dish of Salt", 1982 (Box 96)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 96)
    - Theatre Communications Group Inc. manager's bulletin, 1985 March (Box 96)
    - Cash receipts journal, 1986 (Box 96)
    - IBM, 1980 (Box 97)
    - The Howard Gilman Foundation, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Complaint letters, undated (Box 97)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Bulletin, 1986 (Box 97)
    - Taxes, 1987-1989; 2 (Box 97)
    - Lawsuit and Xerox machine information, 1983 (Box 97)
    - Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 97)
    - Yet another copy fiasco, 1985-1986 (Box 97)
    - Luncheon report, 1982-184 (Box 97)
    - Printing, 1983 (Box 97)
    - Long range plan, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Actor expenses, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Composer/librettist opera studio budget, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Directors payments, 1984 (Box 97)
    - Industry drive status reports, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
    - Lindsay and Crouse studio, undated (Box 97)
    - Tax troubles, 1984-1985 (Box 97)
    - Retax, 1986-1987 (Box 97)
    - McDonald's Award, 1983 (Box 97)
    - Dunhill/doodles auction, 1985 (Box 97)
    - Bi-monthly newsletter request for bids, 1983 (Box 97)
    - Permits, undated (Box 97)
    - Insurance claims, 1979 (Box 97)
    - Playwrights center, undated (Box 97)
    - Contributor lists, 1987 (Box 97)
    - Evaluation of New Dramatists, undated (Box 97)
    - David Copelin receipts, undated (Box 97)
    - Receipts for Joy Blacksmith (Box 97)
    - David Juaire expenses, 1980-1982 (Box 97)
    - Casey Childs expenses, undated (Box 97)
    - Check copies, 1982 (Box 97)
    - Seventh Heaven, undated (Box 97)
    - New Dramatists productions, 1985 (Box 97)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club financial report, 1983 (Box 97)
    - Luncheon playbill advertisement rates, 1983-1984 (Box 97)
    - ScriptShare, undated (Box 97)
    - Playbill award, 1982 (Box 97)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 97)
    - Sharfman, 1978-1981 (Box 97)
    - Industry drive, 1986-1987 (Box 97)
    - Budget comparison, 1986-1988 (Box 97)
    - Proposals, 1983-1987 (Box 97)
    - ARA refreshments, 1986 (Box 97)
    - Proofs, 1988 (Box 97)
    - Bank statements, 1985-1986 (Box 97)
    - Automatic Data Processing, 1986-1987 (Box 97)
    - Artists reimbursement, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Pitney Bowes, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Postage receipts (United States Postal Service), 1980-1987 (Box 98)
    - Federal Express, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Quick Quality Copy, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Silver & Sons Hardware, 1986-1987 (Box 98)
    - Straight Hardware, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Safeguard, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Schildwater, 1987 (Box 98)
    - Richard J. Sica, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Star-Litho, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Traden Stationers, 1986-1987 (Box 98)
    - United Parcel Service, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Balance sheets, 1986-1987; 2 (Box 98)
    - Chemical Bank statements, 1986 July-August (Box 98)
    - Financial journals, undated; 2 (Box 98)
    - Check log, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Payment plans for money owed on missed payments, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Checkbook, 1977-1978 (Box 98)
    - Board committee list, undated (Box 98)
    - Tom Dunn - director's expenses and travel, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Court proceedings, undated (Box 98)
    - Script readings, 1984 (Box 98)
    - Telephone call lists, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 98)
    - Liquor contacts, undated (Box 98)
    - Detail reports, undated (Box 98)
    - Party supplies, 1982-1984 (Box 98)
    - Tax liability, 1986 (Box 98)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Revenues, 1985-1986 (Box 98)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 98)
    - 1099 contracts, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Miscellaneous notes, correspondence, and pamphlets, undated; 2 (Box 98)
    - Dailey report, undated (Box 98)
    - The books, undated (Box 98)
    - Miscellaneous notes, correspondence, and pamphlets, undated (Box 98)
    - Vendor correspondence, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Invoices, 1985 (Box 98)
    - Minneapolis Playwright's Center information, undated (Box 98)
    - Financial records, undated; 2 (Box 99)
    - Composer-librettist, 1987-1989; 3 (Box 100)
    - Amoco Foundation, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, 1981-1986 (Box 100)
    - Alumni, 1986 (Box 100)
    - Altman Foundation, 1988 (Box 100)
    - American Arts Alliance, 1988 (Box 100)
    - Department of Cultural Affairs, 1987-1988; 5 (Box 100)
    - Musical theatre proposal, 1983 (Box 100)
    - National Institute for Music Theater, 1986-1988 (Box 100)
    - Meet the composer, 1987-1989; 2 (Box 100)
    - Manhattan Community Arts Fund, undated (Box 100)
    - Kesselring Awards Committee, 1985 (Box 100)
    - Script analysis, undated (Box 100)
    - Theatre week article, 1988 September (Box 100)
    - Program reports, 1987-1988; 2 (Box 100)
    - Press releases, 1986-1989; 4 (Box 100)
    - New York State Council for the Arts final report, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Artistic report, 1988-1989 (Box 100)
    - Annual report (original), 1988-1989 (Box 100)
    - Articles and miscellany, 1988-1989 (Box 100)
    - Revenue and expense analysis, 1988-1989 (Box 100)
    - Press, 1988-1989; 9 (Box 100)
    - Proposal schedules and charts, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Financial reports, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Application deadlines, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Proposal out charts, 1989 (Box 100)
    - General grant application, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Funding leads, undated (Box 100)
    - Foundation connections prospects, 1989 (Box 100)
    - Billy Rose Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 100)
    - The Heidi Chronicles Benefit, 1989 (Box 100)
    - College mailing list, 1987; 2 (Box 100)
    - Seminar reservations, 1989 June 8 (Box 101)
    - Mark Lutwak's resume, undated (Box 101)
    - Desktop publishing seminar, 1989; 2 (Box 101)
    - "Into The Night", 1991 (Box 101)
    - Staged readings, 1988-1989 (Box 101)
    - Composer/librettist, undated (Box 101)
    - General exchange, undated (Box 101)
    - Mortgage information, 1986-1988 (Box 101)
    - Board and committee files, 1987-1991; 49 (Box 101)
    - General audition schedule, 1984 January 11 (Box 101)
    - Programs, 1981-1986; 4 (Box 101)
    - Applications for stage director, 1983 (Box 101)
    - Applications for musical director, 1983; 2 (Box 101)
    - Applications for composer, 1983 (Box 101)
    - Applications for choreographer, 1983 (Box 101)
    - Member bulletins, 1987 (Box 101)
    - Opera, 1985 (Box 101)
    - Alumni, 1991 (Box 102)
    - 100 monologues, 1988 (Box 102)
    - Commissions, 1989 (Box 102)
    - Opera workshop, 1986; 2 (Box 102)
    - Newsletters, 1989 (Box 102)
    - Admissions, 1988-1989 (Box 102)
    - Opera proposal, 1984 (Box 102)
    - Writer's Guild West, undated (Box 102)
    - Composer-librettist studio, 1987-1988 (Box 102)
    - Teacher applications
      - Herz, Shirley, 1987-1988 (Box 102)
      - Howard, Eleanor Harris, undated (Box 102)
      - Klein, Elaine, 1988-1989 (Box 102)
      - Lafter, Alan, 1987-1988 (Box 102)
      - Lawrence, Jack, 1988 (Box 102)
      - Leslie, F. Andrew, 1989 (Box 102)
    - Long range plan weekly time sheets, undated (Box 102)
    - Police and insurance file, 1986 (Box 102)
    - Audit materials, 1988-1989 (Box 102)
    - Industry drive, 1988; 2 (Box 102)
    - Finances, 1986 (Box 102)
    - Luncheons, 1986-1989; 11 (Box 102)
    - January 14 party, 1960-1961 (Box 102)
    - Sample letters, 1962 (Box 102)
    - Producers project, 1963-1969 (Box 102)
    - Goldman Fund-raising letter and replies, 1969 (Box 102)
    - Reevaluation, 1963-1966 (Box 102)
    - Board of directors, 1960-1961 (Box 102)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1962-1967 (Box 102)
    - Activity report, 1960-1961 (Box 102)
    - New York State Council on the Arts grant expenses, 1963-1964 (Box 102)
    - Records - music publication, 1965-1972 (Box 102)
    - Theatre admissions, 1969-1970 (Box 102)
    - Additional productions, 1960-1961 (Box 102)
    - Alumni, undated (Box 102)
    - History, undated (Box 102)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969; 20 (Box 103)
    - Correspondence from the 1962 drive (Box 103)
    - Campaign, 1968 (Box 103)
    - Fund drive, 1961 (Box 103)
    - Industry committee, 1967 (Box 103)
    - Off Broadway, undated; 7 (Box 103)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1965-1966 (Box 103)
    - Reevaluation, 1963 (Box 103)
    - Premiere productions originals, undated (Box 103)
    - Progress reports, 1970 (Box 103)
    - Reevaluation, 1962 (Box 103)
    - Progress reports, 1968 (Box 103)
    - Reevaluation, 1967 (Box 103)
    - Playwrights letters asking for money, 1967-1979 (Box 103)
    - Miscellaneous files, undated (Box 103)
    - New York Foundation, 1965-1968 (Box 103)
    - Contributions, 1963 (Box 103)
    - Reevaluation, 1965 (Box 103)
    - Rehearsed reading of "Ride a Cockhorse", 1957-1979 (Box 103)
    - Progress reports, 1964 (Box 103)
    - Warg, Rea correspondence, 1961 (Box 103)
    - Whiting, B.J. correspondence, 1958-1961 (Box 103)
    - Rejection letters, undated (Box 103)
    - Memo sheet for sounding panels, undated (Box 103)
    - Letters of application deferment, undated (Box 103)
    - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers, Inc., 1964 (Box 103)
    - Photographic proofs, undated (Box 103)
    - Space planning, undated (Box 103)
    - Rehearsed reading of "The Oldest Profession", 1965 (Box 103)
    - Rehearsed readings
      - "The Boy Who Came to Leave" by Kalcheim, Lee, 1965 (Box 104)
      - "The Ceremonies in Dark Old Men" by Eldar III, Lonne (Box 104)
      - "The Ocean Out Front" by Harvey, James, 1965 (Box 104)
      - "Keep the Pastrami Hot" by Marmorstein, Malcolm, 1965 (Box 104)
      - New play by Kalcheim, Lee, 1965 (Box 105)
    - Open house, 1965 (Box 104)
    - Workshop in action, 1965 (Box 104)
    - Craft discussions
      - Playwright groups, 1963 (Box 104)
      - Second City (Box 104)
      - Designers, 1964 (Box 104)
      - Small groups, 1963 (Box 104)
      - Artaud, Antonin, 1963 (Box 104)
    - Progress reports, 1967 (Box 104)
    - Producers outside of New York, 1965-1968 (Box 104)
    - Producers seeking playwrights, 1964-1966 (Box 104)
    - Progress reports, 1966 (Box 104)
    - Rehearsed reading of "The Gingham Dog" by Wilson, Lanford, 1968 (Box 104)
    - U.S. Internal Revenue, undated (Box 104)
    - Rockefeller lectures, 1960 (Box 104)
    - New Dramatists declaration of intent, 1960-1961 (Box 104)
    - Burman, Howard, 1967-1969 (Box 104)
    - Correspondence, 1967; 2 (Box 104)
    - Fund-raising campaign, 1965; 2 (Box 104)
    - Production-observer program, undated (Box 104)
    - Eastern States Theatre Association, 1961-1962 (Box 104)
    - Activities report, 1960-1964; 2 (Box 104)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1960-1964; 2 (Box 104)
    - Rejected director-observer grant applicants, 1960-1961 (Box 104)
    - Board of directors meeting, 1961 (Box 104)
    - Follow-up, undated (Box 104)
    - New Dramatists Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 104)
    - Applications
      - Unsorted applications, undated (Box 104)
      - Alson, Sheila, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Anderson, Douglas, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Argers, H.V., 1988 (Box 104)
      - Atkin, Louis Phillip, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Banks, Carol, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Barone, Tracey, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Bale, John, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Bates, Allan, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Bedford, Bonnie C., 1988 (Box 104)
      - Beim, Norman, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Bennett Jr., Walter Allen, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Berger, Robert, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Berman, Mark, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Biggs, Billy, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Binkley, Doug, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Bishop, Denise Collette, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Bishop, Conrad and Fuller, Elizabeth, 1989 (Box 104)
      - Blickley, Mark, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Boylan, Daryl, 1988 (Box 104)